{
    "games": [
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "pi\u00e8ce jointe",
                    "content": [
                        " recipient",
                        " attachment ",
                        " bulletin board",
                        " submit"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "le plus t\u00f4t possible",
                    "content": [
                        " rest assured",
                        " bulletin board",
                        " at your earliest convenience",
                        " stationery"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "panneau d'affichage",
                    "content": [
                        " memo",
                        " attachment ",
                        " look forward to",
                        " bulletin board"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "courrier",
                    "content": [
                        " at your earliest convenience",
                        " stamp",
                        " correspondance",
                        " stationery"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "enveloppe",
                    "content": [
                        " zip code",
                        " enveloppe",
                        " inbox",
                        " memo"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "bo\u00eete de r\u00e9ception",
                    "content": [
                        " stationery",
                        " attachment ",
                        " letterhead",
                        " inbox"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "en-t\u00eate",
                    "content": [
                        " letterhead",
                        " postage",
                        " attachment ",
                        " stationery"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "attendre avec impatience",
                    "content": [
                        " look forward to",
                        " attachment ",
                        " postage",
                        " letterhead"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "note de service",
                    "content": [
                        " weight",
                        " memo",
                        " attachment ",
                        " letterhead"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "affranchissement",
                    "content": [
                        " at your earliest convenience",
                        " rest assured",
                        " postage",
                        " weight"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "destinataire",
                    "content": [
                        " at your earliest convenience",
                        " postage",
                        " recipient",
                        " inbox"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "soyez assur\u00e9 que",
                    "content": [
                        " at your earliest convenience",
                        " enveloppe",
                        " rest assured",
                        " correspondance"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "exp\u00e9diteur",
                    "content": [
                        " look forward to",
                        " postage",
                        " inbox",
                        " sender"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "timbre",
                    "content": [
                        " attachment ",
                        " recipient",
                        " stamp",
                        " inbox"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "papeterie",
                    "content": [
                        " at your earliest convenience",
                        " inbox",
                        " stationery",
                        " letterhead"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "soumettre",
                    "content": [
                        " correspondance",
                        " letterhead",
                        " submit",
                        " stationery"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "extr\u00eame",
                    "content": [
                        " bulletin board",
                        " utmost",
                        " letterhead",
                        " stamp"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "poids",
                    "content": [
                        " utmost",
                        " sender",
                        " rest assured",
                        " weight"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "code postal",
                    "content": [
                        " stationery",
                        " submit",
                        " at your earliest convenience",
                        " zip code"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}